(Sheldon:)Why are we all here?
Because we're scientists.
(Sheldon:)And what do scientists study?
(Sheldon:)The universe.
(Sheldon:)And what's the universe made of?
(Sheldon:)I am so glad you asked.
[SINGING] There's antimony, arsenic
Aluminum, selenium
(Sheldon:)Hydrogen and oxygen
And nitrogen and rhenium
(Sheldon:)And nickel, neodymium
Neptunium, germanium
Everybody!
And iron, americium
Ruthenium, uranium
Europium, zirconium
Lutetium, vanadium
Just the Asians!
And lanthanum and osmium
And astatine and radium
(Sheldon:)Penny, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Would you be able to answer
some questions I'm having...
(Sheldon:)...about the events of last night?
(Sheldon:)-Sure.
-Question one.